<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get Started on Singleton</title>
    <link>https://vmware.github.io/singleton/docs/get-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Get Started on Singleton</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 22:58:29 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vmware.github.io/singleton/docs/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Download and Installation</title>
      <link>https://vmware.github.io/singleton/docs/get-started/download-and-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 20:04:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vmware.github.io/singleton/docs/get-started/download-and-installation/</guid>
      <description>Singleton official 0.1.0 Release is available now! Choose the download that&amp;rsquo;s right for you and click one of the links below.
Singleton Service 0.1.0 Binaries Downloading filename sha1 hash branch/tag singleton-manager-i18n-0.1.0.jar 8e7599495292ce34cdb9769ec43695999071a1fe master/v0.1.0-Singleton-Service singleton-manager-l10n-0.1.0.jar 8d744bb83e310a1b451a68fb65999803488c8cfc master/v0.1.0-Singleton-Service Installation Singleton Service include 2 types of builds, one is i18n manager, the other is l10n manager:
I18n manager is the main build, it provides the restful APIs to talk with Singleton SDK. L10n manager will work together with I18n manager to achieve the feature Source Collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start</title>
      <link>https://vmware.github.io/singleton/docs/get-started/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 20:04:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vmware.github.io/singleton/docs/get-started/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>The Singleton application suite includes:
Singleton Service: It contains an Application Program Interface (API), which is a web service that is used for i18n features, such as providing translated text. Singleton Client: It is used to communicate with Singleton Service to get the localized resources. Features and functionality Singleton offers the following features and functionality:
Singleton Core API - Provides RESTful web services for delivering localized resources. Source collection - Offers a source collection feature for Singleton string-based APIs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
